Danny Kaye and Sylvia Fine Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1939-1985 (Box 1-427, 536-537, 641-765, 791)
  - Sylvia Fine, 1940s-1970s
    - Happy ending, Manuscript full score, printed piano-vocal score, lyric sheets (Box-folder 421/8, 626/2)
    - Happy times, Printed score, sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 421/9)
    - I could like him a lot, Music by Ben Weisman; lyric by Sylvia Fine; Lead sheets, lyric sheets (Box-folder 421/10)
    - I keep humming the tune, By Sylvia Fine and Sy Miller; Manuscript score (Box-folder 421/11)
    - I like Marie, Lead sheet, lyric sheets (Box-folder 421/12)
    - I live to love, Lead sheet, lyric sheets (Box-folder 421/13)
    - Icebox, Manuscript piano part (Box-folder 421/14, 521)
    - If you were gone from me, Manuscript piano score (Box-folder 421/15)
    - ILGWU, Sketches, lyric sheet (Box-folder 421/16)
    - In love again, Manuscript scores, sketch, lyric sheets (Box-folder 421/17, 626/3)
    - Information please, Manuscript score, lyric sheets (Box-folder 421/18)
    - Jack & Jill, Sketches (Box-folder 421/19)
    - Japanese song (ami ami), Sketch (Box-folder 421/20)
    - Knock on wood, Manuscript and printed scores, sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 422/1)
    - Korean song, Manuscript score (Box-folder 422/2)
    - Laugh it off, Lead sheet, lyric sheets (Box-folder 422/3)
    - Let's make love, Sketches (Box-folder 422/4)
    - Liddle fiddle, Lead sheet, lyric sheets (Box-folder 422/5)
    - Life could not better be, By Sylvia Fine and Sammy Cahn; Printed scores, lyric sheets (Box-folder 422/6)
    - The little child, Manuscript and printed scores, lyric sheets (Box-folder 422/7)
    - Lobby number, Short score, lyric sheets; Includes sketch of "New fanfare." (Box-folder 422/8)
    - Lone ranger, Sketches; Includes sketches of "Schlepp." (Box-folder 422/9)
    - Love me again, Lead sheet, lyric sheets (Box-folder 422/10)
    - Lullabye in ragtime, Manuscript and printed scores, sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 422/11, 694/9)
    - Lyrics, Manuscript and typescript lyric sheets, scripts, and scenarios; Includes several Danny Kaye Show scripts and election parody songs
      - A (Box-folder 536/1)
        About Face
        Admiral Schlepp
        All My Husbands
        All My Life
        All the Words
        Alma Mater
        Alone at Last
        Auld Lang Syne
      - B (Box-folder 536/2)
        Barking Doggerel
        Baseball Around the World - script and lyrics
        Before Love
        Bettina
        Beware
        The Bon Vivant
        Bond Song - Danny Kaye Show 5-12-1945 - script and lyrics
        Boy Meets Girl
        Brooklyn College Prize Songs
        Brooklyn for Beginners
        Bryllcream ala Bellafonte
        By the Beautiful Sea
      - C (Box-folder 536/3)
        Camp Cast Karaway
        Casey - script
        Coccayanakoos
        Collasal Tot
        Congressman Opening
        Constantinople
      - D (Box-folder 536/4)
        Daniel the Great Social Lion
        Dead End Kids
        Deb on the Debit Side
        Der Richtig Mikado
        Desire Under the Elms
        Doman, Doman, Domani
        Downing Street
        Dream
        Dream Sequence
        Durocher Dinner
      - F (Box-folder 536/5)
        Fish Story
        Folk Song
        For All I Know
        From the Top of the City
      - G (Box-folder 536/6)
        Game Sketch
        Gardner Cowles
        The Great Chandelier
        The Great Escape March
        The Great White Way Is in the Pink Today
      - H (Box-folder 536/7)
        Harbour Lights
        Harry
        Heart of My Heart
        Heigh Ho and Lullaby Low
        Here He Comes Now - sketch
        Hole in the Bottom of the Sea
        How About You
        How to Behave Tho' an Audience
        How to Speak Brooklyn - routine
        Husband-Wife-Lover
      - I (Box-folder 536/8)
        I Catch On
        I Keep Remembering
        I Like to Be beside the Seaside
        I Made a Fool of Myself
        I'd Rather Be Wrong
        I'm Late
        I'm Young Again
        I've Got a Date with Uncle Sam
        If I'm Elected
        Intermission
        It Feels Like Saturday Night
      - J (Box-folder 536/9)
        Jitterbug
      - K (Box-folder 536/10)
        Kabuki - scenario
      - M (Box-folder 536/11)
        Maggie
        Majorca
        Marty
        Meier and Franks
      - N (Box-folder 537/1)
        Not Another Cent
      - O (Box-folder 537/2)
        Oh Mr. Horton
        Oh, Tell Me Pretty Maiden
        Opening Opening
        Our Saturday Night Opening
      - P (Box-folder 537/3)
        Picnic in the Snow
        Pick Aly
        Polynesian Scenario
        The Portions of a Woman
      - R (Box-folder 537/4)
        Radio Farewell
        RAF Number
        Restaurant Sketch
        Richard Burton
        Ring Up the Curtain Opening
        Rock-a-Bye
        Round for Johnson
        Round the World Number
      - S (Box-folder 537/5-6)
        Saints
        Sammy Cahn Anniversary
        Schnitzelbank
        School for Commercials
        Sea Chanty
        Show Business
        Show Must Go On Opening
        Shubert Alley
        Sign of the Times
        So in Love - Patter for Vera Ellen - script and lyrics
        Soap Opera - skit
        Some Enchanted Garden - ballet outline
        Sorry of Songs - script and lyrics
        South American Way - Danny Kaye Show 15-A; script and lyrics
        Spies
        The Sun and I
        Sweet Alice
        Swept by the Breeze
        Swifty, the Anitseptic Traveler
      - T (Box-folder 537/7)
        The Tamiment Players Present
        Tamure
        There'll Be Some Changes Made
        Times - script and lyrics
        Tom, Tom, the Piper's Son - script and lyrics
        Toreador Song - Vote for Johnson
        TV Commercials
        Two Cups of Coffee - skit script
        Typhoon - skit
      - U (Box-folder 537/8)
        Understudy
      - V (Box-folder 537/9)
        Viva Romantic Romance - script and lyrics
      - W (Box-folder 537/10)
        War Fund Song
        We Gotta Find Bill
        What Suits My Fancy - script and lyrics
        When Manuelo Makes with the Maraccas
        When There's a Moon
        Why - opera
        Why, Mommy?
        Why Should I Try
        Wish You Were Here
        Wolf of Wall Street- opera?
      - Y (Box-folder 537/11)
        Yes Mr. Maniac
        You Touch My Heart
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 537/11)
    - Main title from Man with the golden arm, Manuscript short score, piano-vocal scores, sketch (Box-folder 626/4)
    - Make love, my love, Music by Vic Schoen, lyric by Sylvia Fine; Manuscript piano score (Box-folder 423/1)
    - Marriage-go-round, Manuscript scores, lyric sheets (Box-folder 423/2)
    - Melody in 4-F, Manuscript score (Box-folder 423/3)
    - Midsummer madness, Manuscript piano score (Box-folder 423/4)
    - Mine alone, Manuscript lead sheets; Includes sketches of "Gypsy tea kettle" and "You can see for yourself" on verso. (Box-folder 423/5)
    - Miscellany, Lyric sheets and Herbert Baker's The student guerilla (Box-folder 423/6)
    - Miscellany, Lyric sheets and notes in folder titled "Danny Kaye Show" (Box-folder 423/7)
    - Miscellaneous lyrics, Lyric sheets in folder titled "Incomplete lyrics" (Box-folder 423/8)
    - Miscellany, Lyric sheets in folder titled "Lyrics - pending" (Box-folder 423/9)
    - Miscellany, Sketches; On envelope: Isolated music SFK working on. (Box-folder 423/10-11)
    - Miscellany, Sketches; On envelope: Musicals.; Includes sketches for Court Jester, "Blue ribbon blues", "Two-part invention", and "Don't you think." (Box-folder 626/5)
    - Miscellany, Sketches; On envelope: Unfinished scraps.; Includes student exercises and sketches for "We're a whole new thing." (Box-folder 626/6)
    - Miscellany, Sketches and fragments (Box-folder 423/12)
    - Miscellany, Annotated copy of G. Wedge's Keyboard Harmony (Box-folder 424/1)
    - Molly-o, Manuscript and printed scores, sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 424/2)
    - The Moon is blue, By Sylvia Fine and Herschel Burke Gilbert; Printed scores (Box-folder 424/3)
    - My heart knows a lovely song, By Sylvia Fine and Sammy Cahn; Printed scores, lyric sheets (Box-folder 424/4)
    - Nashville, Tennessee, By Sylvia Fine and Herb Baker; Manuscript vocal part, lyric sheets (Box-folder 424/5)
    - No for an answer blues, Manuscript piano part, lyric sheet (Box-folder 424/6)
    - No two people, Lyric sheets; Alternative lyrics for Musical Comedy Tonight, annotated "Cue Magazine Entertainer of the Year." (Box-folder 424/7)
    - The "no-where blues", Music by Herschel Burke Gilbert, lyrics by Sylvia Fine; Printed score (Box-folder 424/8)
    - On the double, Printed scores, sketch (Box-folder 424/9)
    - On the Riviera, Manuscript full score, printed piano-vocal scores, sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 424/10)
    - Once there was music, Sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 424/11)
    - Only yesterday, Music by Ben Weisman; lyrics by Sylvia Fine; Manuscript lead sheets (Box-folder 424/12)
    - Opera number for Wonder man, Manuscript score (Box-folder 424/13)
    - Operetta/revue ["I need a pair of dancin' shoes"], Sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 424/14)
    - Orchi-chornia, Lyric sheet and description of action (Box-folder 424/15)
    - Pass the basket, Lyric sheets, sketches (Box-folder 424/16)
    - Pavlova, Manuscript full score, piano-vocal score, sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 424/17)
    - Popo the puppet, Printed score, lyric sheets (Box-folder 425/1)
    - Rhyme, Sketches (Box-folder 425/2)
    - Rhythm of a new romance, Sketch, lyric sheets (Box-folder 425/3)
    - Romeo and Juliet calypso, Sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 425/4)
    - The snark and whistle, Lyric sheets; Includes "At the pub." (Box-folder 425/5)
    - Sketchbooks [#1-2], undated, Student exercises and compositions (Box-folder 425/6-7)
    - Sketchbooks [#3-4], undated (Box-folder 425/8-9)
    - Soliloquy for three heads, Lyric sheets (Box-folder 425/10)
    - Stanislavsky, Manuscript short score, piano-vocal score, lyric sheets (Box-folder 425/111)
    - Stickfitz, Other title: Shickfitz; Manuscript short score, piano-vocal score, lyric sheets (Box-folder 425/12)
    - Suzanne, Music by George Duning; lyrics by Sylvia Fine; Printed scores, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/1)
    - There's a hole, Lead sheet (Box-folder 426/2)
    - Things to forget, By Sylvia Fine and Ben Weisman; Other title: Things I should forget; Manuscript scores, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/3)
    - Triple mirror, Sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/4)
    - Uncle pockets, Printed scores, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/5)
    - A vote for Jones, Sketch, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/6)
    - Waltzing Matilda, Manuscript piano score (Box-folder 426/7)
    - Wee you no come back again, Manuscript piano score (Box-folder 426/8)
    - We're a whole new thing, Sketches, lyric sheets, reference materials (Box-folder 426/9)
    - What happens to love, Sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/10)
    - When it's cherry blossom time in Orange New Jersey, Sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/11)
    - Who tells the ants, Sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/12)
    - Will you be with me, By Sylvia Fine and Elmer Bernstein; Lead sheets (Box-folder 426/13)
    - Willow willow waley, Sketches, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/14)
    - Wish I may, Score, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/15)
    - Yogi, Manuscript piano-vocal score, piano part, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/16)
    - Yon-u-ary, Lead sheets, lyric sheets (Box-folder 426/17)
    - You gotta love everybody, Sketches (Box-folder 426/18)
    - You took my heart, Sketches (Box-folder 426/19)
  - Music by Other Composers, 1951-1971
    Chiefly manuscript scores and lead sheets.
    - Black Coffee, undated, Score; violin (annotated), saxophone, and trumpet parts; By Maurice Sigler, Al Goodhart, and Al Hoffman; Arranged by Paul Weirick; Includes note from Larry to Sam regarding Danny Kaye and the song. (Box-folder 791/1)
    - Down on downing street, By Sylvia French; Score (Box-folder 427/1)
    - The fiddle that went west, Music by Paul Nero; story and lyrics by Sheldon Allman; Score (Box-folder 427/2)
    - Fifty Stars, Music by Joseph Meyer; lyrics by Joseph A. McCarthy; Lead sheet, cover letter (Box-folder 427/3)
    - Happy, By Fred Freed; Score, cover letter; From envelope "Music submitted to S.K. for lyrics." (Box-folder 427/4)
    - The happy international family, By Sally Webber and Lou Snider; Lead sheet, cover letter (Box-folder 427/5)
    - I like you, By Loyal Nichols; Lead sheet, note (Box-folder 427/6)
    - It's time; On the first day of Christmas, Arranged by Jimmy Carroll; Lead sheets, script introductions, correspondence; For UNICEF. (Box-folder 427/7)
    - Lager beer, Music by Edward Marshall; lyrics by Julius Rutin; Lead sheet (Box-folder 427/8)
    - Makin' love to you, Music by Roy Alfred; lyrics by Ben Weisman; Lead sheets (Box-folder 427/9)
    - The mysterious people, Music by Olle Adolphson; lyrics by Hal Shaper; Lead sheet (Box-folder 427/10)
    - O moon above, By George Arno and Walton Farrar; Lead sheet (Box-folder 427/11)
    - The plough, By Earl E. Lawrence; Lead sheets (Box-folder 427/12)
    - Ringo no uta (Song of the apple), By Tadushi Manjomi and Hachiro Sato; Lead sheet; Note: Contained in songbook (Box-folder 427/29)
    - Romeova casanova valentine d'amore, By The Brothers Cain; Lead sheet (Box-folder 427/13)
    - Rosalie Farber, Music by Stan Worth; lyrics by Arthur Hamilton; Lead sheet (Box-folder 427/14)
    - The secret of the purple reef, By Walter Kent and Walton Farrar; Lead sheet (Box-folder 427/15)
    - Shino no yoru (China night), By Ryōichi Hattori; Lead sheet; Note: Contained in songbook (Box-folder 427/29)
    - Tell me why?, By Don Crawford and Bill Bennett; Score, lead sheets (Box-folder 427/16)
    - To Danny Kaye, By J. Langerdoen; Score, lead sheet (Box-folder 427/17)
    - To make you happy, Music by David Saxon; lyrics by Sammy Gallop; Lead sheets (Box-folder 427/18)
    - Under the kissin' tree, By Don Crawford; Lead sheets, lyric sheet (Box-folder 427/19)
    - Varsity drag, By B. G. deSylva, Lew Brown, and Ray Henderson; Sheet music (Box-folder 427/20)
    - Waiting by the sea, By Don Crawford and Tony Ladanchuk; Lead sheets (Box-folder 427/21)
    - The wine of the moon, Music by Irv Orton; lyrics by Tony Barr; Lead sheet (Box-folder 427/22)
    - Would he mind, By Don Crawford; Score, lead sheets (Box-folder 427/23)
    - Yerushalayim Shel Zahav, Arranged by Erwin Jospe; Score, lyric sheet (Box-folder 427/24)
    - You crossed your fingers, By Don Crawford; Score, lead sheets (Box-folder 427/25)
    - Your own thing, By Hal Hester and Danny Apolinar; Lead sheets, program (Box-folder 427/26)
    - Unidentified, By David Kapp; Score; From envelope "Music submitted to S.K. for lyrics." (Box-folder 427/27)
    - Unidentified, By Abram Chasins; Sketches; From envelope "Music submitted to S.K. for lyrics." (Box-folder 427/28)
- Scripts, 1944-1986 (Box-folder 443-482)
  Scripts from the The Danny Kaye Radio Show, The Danny Kaye Show, The John Gary Show, films, stand-alone television programs, and theatrical productions. Scripts for Musical Comedy Tonight are found here.
  Arranged by production series.
  - The Danny Kaye Radio Show, 1944-1946
    Radio scripts.
    Arranged chronologically by episode date.
    - 1944 December - 1945 January - April (Box-folder 443/1-17)
    - 1945 May - 1946 February (Box-folder 444/1-21)
    - 1946 March - May (Box-folder 445/1-13)
  - Danny Kaye Specials, 1960-1963
    Television scripts.
    - An Hour with Danny Kaye, 1960, October (Box-folder 446/1)
    - The Danny Kaye Show with Lucille Ball, 1963, October - November (Box-folder 446/2-3)
  - The Danny Kaye Show, 1963-1967
    Arranged numerically by episode number. Library of Congress record numbers provide links to the full catalog record for each episode, including production information. Multiple record numbers indicate episodes for which there are excerpts and/or outakes.
    - Episode #1, 1963, September 25, 95502768 (Box-folder 447/1)
    - Episode #2, 1963 October 2, 95503396 (Box-folder 447/2)
    - Episode #3, 1964, March 11, 95503412 (Box-folder 447/3)
    - Episode #4, 1963, October 9, 95503449 (Box-folder 447/4)
    - Episode #5, 1963, October 23, 95503551 (Box-folder 447/5)
    - Episode #6, 1963, October 16, 95503706; 95503715 (Box-folder 448/1)
    - Episode #7, 1963, November 20, 95503717 (Box-folder 448/2)
    - Episode #8, 1964, February 12, 95503906 (Box-folder 448/3)
    - Episode #9, 1964, January 1, 95503909 (Box-folder 448/4)
    - Episode #10, 1963, October 30, 95503930 (Box-folder 448/5)
    - Episode #11, 1963, November 6, 95504257 (Box-folder 449/1)
    - Episode #12, 1963, November 13, 95504260 (Box-folder 449/2)
    - Episode #13, 1963, November 27, 95504292 (Box-folder 449/3)
    - Episode #14, 1963, December 4, 95504305 (Box-folder 449/4)
    - Episode #15, 1963, December 11, 95504328 (Box-folder 449/5)
    - Episode #16, 1963, December 18, 95504337 (Box-folder 449/6)
    - Episode #17, 1963, December 25, 95504339 (Box-folder 450/1)
    - Episode #18, 1964, January 8, 95504343 (Box-folder 450/2)
    - Episode #19, 1964, January 15, 95504361; 95504365 (Box-folder 450/3)
    - Episode #20, 1964, January 22, 95504373 (Box-folder 450/4)
    - Episode #21, 1964, January 29, 95504377 (Box-folder 450/5)
    - Episode #22, 1964, February 5, 95504540 (Box-folder 450/6)
    - Episode #23, 1964, February 19, 95504782 (Box-folder 451/1)
    - Episode #24, 1964, February 26, 95504862 (Box-folder 451/2)
    - Episode #25, 1964, March 4, 95505229 (Box-folder 451/3)
    - Episode #26, 1964, March 25, 95505041 (Box-folder 451/4)
    - Episode #27, 1964, March 18, 95505143 (Box-folder 451/5)
    - Episode #28, 1964, April 1, 95505230 (Box-folder 451/6)
    - Episode #29, 1964, April 8, 95505406; 95505454 (Box-folder 451/7)
    - Episode #30, 1964, April 15, 95505559 (Box-folder 452/1)
    - Episode #31, 1964, April 22, 95505681 (Box-folder 452/2)
    - Episode #32, 1964, April 29, 95505758; 95506185 (Box-folder 452/3)
    - Episode #33, 1964, November 25, 95506002 (Box-folder 452/4)
    - Episode #34, 1964, October 21, 95506008 (Box-folder 452/5)
    - Episode #35, 1964, September 23, 95506488 (Box-folder 452/6)
    - Episode #36, 1964, February 10, 95506557 (Box-folder 453/1)
    - Episode #37, 1964, December 30, 95506611; 95507058; 95507063 (Box-folder 453/2)
    - Episode #38, 1964, October 28, 95507692 (Box-folder 453/3)
    - Episode #39, 1964, September 30, 95507895 (Box-folder 453/4)
    - Episode #40, 1964, October 7, 95508025 (Box-folder 453/5)
    - Episode #41, 1964, October 14, 95508243 (Box-folder 454/1)
    - Episode #42, 1964, November 4, 95508332; 95508359 (Box-folder 454/2)
    - Episode #43, 1965, March 17, 95508405 (Box-folder 454/3)
    - Episode #44, 1964, November 11, 95508565 (Box-folder 454/4)
    - Episode #45, 1964, November 18, 95508803 (Box-folder 454/5)
    - Episode #46, 1964, December 2, 95508805 (Box-folder 454/6)
    - Episode #47, 1964, December 9, 95508806 (Box-folder 455/1)
    - Episode #48, 1964, December 16, 95508981 (Box-folder 455/2)
    - Episode #49, 1964, December 23, 95508998 (Box-folder 455/3)
    - Episode #50, 1965, January 6, 95508999 (Box-folder 455/4)
    - Episode #51, 1965, January 13, 95509142 (Box-folder 455/5)
    - Episode #52, 1965, Jauary 20, 95509303 (Box-folder 455/6)
    - Episode #53, 1965, January 27, 95509315 (Box-folder 456/1)
    - Episode #54, 1965, February 3, 95509334 (Box-folder 456/2)
    - Episode #55, 1965, February 17, 95509409 (Box-folder 456/3)
    - Episode #56, 1965, February 24, 95509458 (Box-folder 456/4)
    - Episode #57, 1965, March 3, 95509662 (Box-folder 456/5)
    - Episode #58, 1965, March 10, 95509663 (Box-folder 456/6)
    - Episode #59, 1965, March 24, 95509705 (Box-folder 457/1)
    - Episode #60, 1965, March 31, 95509707 (Box-folder 457/2)
    - Episode #61, 1965, April 7, 95509781 (Box-folder 457/3)
    - Episode #62, 1965, April 14, 95509983 (Box-folder 457/4)
    - Episode #63, 1965, April 21, 95510104 (Box-folder 457/5)
    - Episode #64, 1965, April 28, 95510202 (Box-folder 458/1)
    - Episode #65, 1966, April 13, 95510272 (Box-folder 458/2)
    - Episode #66, 1965, December 1, 95510594 (Box-folder 458/3)
    - Episode #67, 1965, September 22, 95510595; 95510596 (Box-folder 458/4)
    - Episode #68, 1965, September 29, 95510597 (Box-folder 458/5)
    - Episode #69, 1965, October 6, 95510715; 95510721 (Box-folder 459/1)
    - Episode #70, 1965, September 15, 95510737; 95510738 (Box-folder 459/2)
    - Episode #71, 1965, October 13, 95510920 (Box-folder 459/3)
    - Episode #72, 1966, January 12, 95510996 (Box-folder 459/4)
    - Episode #73, 1965, December 29, 95510999 (Box-folder 459/5)
    - Episode #74, 1965, October 27, 95511332 (Box-folder 459/6)
    - Episode #75, 1965, November 3, 95511333 (Box-folder 460/1)
    - Episode #76, 1965, November 10, 95511334 (Box-folder 460/2)
    - Episode #77, 1965, November 24, 95511363 (Box-folder 460/3)
    - Episode #78, 1965, November 17, 95511335 (Box-folder 460/4)
    - Episode #79, 1965, December 8, 95511364 (Box-folder 460/5)
    - Episode #80, 1966, January 1, 95511367 (Box-folder 461/1)
    - Episode #81, 1965, December 15, 95511530 (Box-folder 461/2)
    - Episode #82, 1965, December 22, 95511574 (Box-folder 461/3-4)
    - Episode #83, 1966, January 5, 95511588 (Box-folder 461/5)
    - Episode #84, 1966, January 26, 95511640 (Box-folder 462/1)
    - Episode #85, 1966, February 2, 95511809 (Box-folder 462/2)
    - Episode #86, 1966, February 9, 95512164; 95512165 (Box-folder 462/3)
    - Episode #87, 1966, February 23, 95512166 (Box-folder 462/4)
    - Episode #88, 1966, February 16, 95512214; 95512219 (Box-folder 462/5)
    - Episode #89, 1966, March 9, 95512225 (Box-folder 462/6)
    - Episode #90, 1966, March 2, 95512296 (Box-folder 463/1)
    - Episode #91, 1966, March 30, 95512657 (Box-folder 463/2)
    - Episode #92, 1966, April 6, 95512658 (Box-folder 463/3)
    - Episode #93, 1966, March 23, 95512659 (Box-folder 463/4)
    - Episode #94, 1966, April 20, 95512660 (Box-folder 463/5)
    - Episode #95, 1966, September 21, 95517712 (Box-folder 464/1)
    - Episode #96, 1966, September 14, 95518058 (Box-folder 464/2)
    - Episode #97, 1967, February 8, 95518102 (Box-folder 464/3)
    - Episode #98, 1966, September 28, 95518115 (Box-folder 464/4)
    - Episode #99, 1966, October 26, 95518235 (Box-folder 465/1)
    - Episode #100, 1966, October 12, 95518266 (Box-folder 465/2)
    - Episode #101, 1966, October 5, 95518307 (Box-folder 465/3)
    - Episode #102, 1966, October 19, 95518444 (Box-folder 465/4)
    - Episode #103, 1966, December 28, 95518495 (Box-folder 465/5)
    - Episode #104, 1966, November 16, 95518503 (Box-folder 466/1)
    - Episode #105, 1966, November 2, 95518574 (Box-folder 466/2)
    - Episode #106, 1967, January 11, 95518650 (Box-folder 466/3)
    - Episode #107, 1967, January 4, 95518809 (Box-folder 466/4)
    - Episode #108, 1966, November 23, 95518916 (Box-folder 466/5)
    - Episode #109, 1966, November 30, 95518972 (Box-folder 467/1)
    - 447/110, 1966, December 7, 95518983 (Box-folder 467/2)
    - Episode #111, 1966, December 14, 95519058 (Box-folder 467/3-4)
    - Episode #112, 1966, December 21, 95519065 (Box-folder 467/5)
    - Episode #113, 1967, March 1, 95519401 (Box-folder 468/1)
    - Episode #114, 1967, January 18, 95519490 (Box-folder 468/2)
    - Episode #115, 1967, January 25, 95519496 (Box-folder 468/3)
    - Episode #116, 1967, February 15, 95519560 (Box-folder 468/4)
    - Episode #117, 1967, February 1, 95519568 (Box-folder 468/5)
    - Episode #118, 1967, February 22, 95519821 (Box-folder 469/1)